<chapter>
	<npcs>
		<situation>The kid is in his school's playground with his friends between classes. They are looking forward to play football, but there are an odd number of players, so they need one more. The kid decides to ask the new student if he wishes to join them.</situation>
		<npc name="Jimmy">
			<dialogue id="A">
				<text>Hey, new kid! Wanna join us playing football? We need one more player.
          </text>
				<answer>Hey there, thanks. I would love to play with you, but I cannot play football.
          </answer>
				<options>
					<option action="dialogueA">Why? Is there something wrong?</option>
					<option action="dialogueB">Why not? You don't look sick or anything.</option>
				</options>
			</dialogue>
			<dialogue id="B">
				<text></text>
				<answer>Yes, I have a disease called Charcot-Marie-Tooth. It makes it really hard for me to maintain balance and control my body like you.</answer>
				<options>
					<option action="dialogueAA">Oh, I'm sorry to hear that. If you want, I can ask the guys to play something other than football so you can join us.</option>
					<option action="dialogueAB">Oh, I'm sorry to hear that. I guess we'll have to play with an odd number of players, then. See you later!</option>
					<option action="dialogueAC">You can be the goalkeeper, then. You won't have to move too much and we get to play with an even number of players</option>
					<option action="dialogueAD">I guess no one will want to play with you then. I'll try to find someone else.</option>
				</options>
			</dialogue>
			<dialogue id="C">
				<text></text>
				<answer>You shouldn't assume things just by looking at people. I'm not sick, but I actually have this disease called Charcot-Marie-Tooth. It makes it really hard for me to maintain balance and control my body like you.</answer>
				<options>
					<option action="dialogueBA">I'm sorry I said that. That was rude. If you want, I can ask the guys to play something other than football so you can join us.</option>
					<option action="dialogueBB">I'm sorry I said that. That was rude. I guess we'll have to play with an odd number of players, then. See you later!</option>
					<option action="dialogueBC">You can be the goalkeeper, then. You won't have to move too much and we get to play with an even number of players.</option>
					<option action="dialogueBD">Who cares? No one will want to play with you, then. I'll try to find someone else.</option>
				</options>
			</dialogue>
		</npc>
	</npcs>
</chapter>